xxxkinky.com 2018-06-28

# Privacy

## xxxkinky.com Privacy Policy

Last updated: June 2018

## 1\. _Introduction_

Thank you for visiting the xxxkinky.com website (the "Website"). Your privacy and the integrity of any information you provide are important to us (“Company; We”), the operator of this Website.

We are accountable for our Privacy Policy and the practices on our Website, including the Privacy Policy as set out below. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please address them via e-mail as below.

This Website may be connected by "hyperlinks" to other third party sites. We are not responsible in any way for the privacy practices on other third party's sites and suggest that you review the privacy policies on those linked sites before using them.

Any information stored on our Website is treated as confidential. All information is stored securely and is accessed by authorized personnel only. The Company implements and maintains appropriate technical, security and organizational measures to protect Personal Data against unauthorized or unlawful processing and use, and against accidental loss, destruction, damage, theft or disclosure.

## 2\. _Collection and Use_

### 2.1 .General

The following sections cover the specifics of each of the three groups from which Personal Data is collected: Website Visitors, Users and Partners. For the purposes of this Policy Personal Data shall mean and may comprise: IP address, first and last name, postal and email address, telephone number, data from social networks, areas of interest, interest in products, as well as information as to the type of relationship that exists between the Company and Visitors, Users and/or Partners.

### 2.2 Website Visitors and Users

By visiting the Website, you consent to the collection and use of your Personal Data as described herein. If you do not agree with the terms set out herein, please do not visit this Website. If required by applicable law, Company will seek your explicit consent to process Personal Data collected on this Website or volunteered by you. Kindly note that any consent will be entirely voluntary. However, if you do not grant the requested consent to the processing of your Personal Data, the use of this Website may not be possible. We may collect, record and analyze information of Visitors to this Website. We may record your IP address and use cookies (see: _Cookie_ _Policy_  ). We may add information collected by way of page view activity. Furthermore, Company may collect and process any Personal Data that you volunteer to us in our website’s forms, such as when you subscribe or sign up for information and newsletters. If you provide Company with your social media details, the Company may retrieve publicly available information about you from social media. The Company gathers data about visits to the website, including numbers of Visitors and visits, Geo-location data, length of time spent on the site, pages clicked on or where Visitors have come.

We comply with all the processing operations in line with the [EU General Data Protection Regulation (hereinafter “GDPR”)](https://www.eugdpr.org/). Recently we have updated our Privacy Policy to account for GDPR provisions. We have added clear explanations of what type of personal data we collect and how we use the data and who we share the data with, including your choices, rights, and controls of your personal information.

Visitors to our Website and services will have multiple manners of interactivity with us. Depending upon Your level of interaction, We will collect different information about You. The type of information collected is as follows:

  1. Members - Members are those Users who interact with our services in a way which requires registration, such as by uploading content to the Website. Members will be prompted to provide a valid e-mail address and password in the process of registering a username. If You want to take full advantage of the verified user We offer, We might also ask You to create a publicly visible introduction, which may include Your photo or video with You.

  2. Browsers - Browsers are visitors to the Website who never enter into any active data collection pages. Browsers may, however, view content uploaded by Members. Any information gathered from Browsers is also gathered from Members. This information is restricted to cookies, IP Addresses and Referral URLs, and other passive information gathering devices.

### 2.3 How We Collect Information

Passive Collection – We use cookies to collect information about You in order to enhance Your experience on the Website. The information that we collect includes, but is not limited to, Your User IP address, geographic location and other session data (device and browser type, language, operating system, the pages or features of our Website or Service to which a user browsed, the time spent on those pages or features, the frequency with which the Service is used by a user, search terms used by a user, the links on the Service that a user clicked on or used, and other statistics).

Active Collection – We collect information from You, such as Your username, e-mail address and password, when You complete registration forms to sign up for Your membership on Our Site. Locations for such collection are registration or personal profile pages, but We reserve the right to add additional information collection portals.

### 2.4 Cookies

The Website and some of our services use cookies (small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters that we put on your computer) and other similar tracking technologies (like web beacons, tags and scripts) to uniquely identify Visitors' and/or Users' browser and to gather information about how Visitor and/or User interact with the Websites and services. We use this information for the following purposes: Assisting Visitor and/or User in navigation; Assisting in registration, login and the ability to provide feedback; Analyzing the use of products, services or applications; and assisting with promotional and marketing efforts (including behavioral advertising).

Please see the Company's  _Cookie_ _Policy_  for more information about the type of cookies and tracking technologies that we use on this Website and why, and how to accept or reject them.

### 2.5 Links to other sites

Please be aware that while visiting the Website, Visitors and/or Users can follow links to other sites that are beyond the Company's control of influence. The Company is not responsible for the content or privacy policy of these other sites.

### 2.6 Users

#### 2.6.1. General

In order to provide services to its Users, the Company collects certain types of data from them. This section will describe how these two types of data are collected and used by the Company as well as geographical differences that effect this policy.

#### 2.6.2 Collection of User data

During a User’s registration and later on the Company’s Website, it provides information such as name, email, address, telephone, credit-card number and other relevant data. This information is used by the Company to identify the User and provide them with support, services, mailings, sales and marketing actions, billing and to meet contractual obligations.

The Company's Users can at any time access and edit, update or delete their contact details by logging in with their username and password. The Company will not retain User's data longer than it is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations.

#### 2.6.3 Collection and Processing of Personal Data

The Company relies on the consent of the individual to process Personal Data (for example, when the user inputs personal information into the Website). On other occasions, the Company may process Personal Data when it needs to do this to fulfill a contract or where it is required to do so by law.

The Company may also process Personal Data when it is in its or its Partners' legitimate interests to do so and when these interests are not overridden by the individual’s data protection rights (which may vary based on an individual’s jurisdiction).

#### 2.6.4. Geographical location

The Company offers a number of data regions. A “Data Region” is a set of data centers located within a defined geographical area where Visitor and/or User data is stored. Personal Data is not transmitted between Data Regions. For Visitor and/or User with accounts located in European Data Region, all Personal Data is processed in the EEA. For Visitor and/or User with accounts in the Data Regions: United States of America (US), all Personal Data is processed solely in the respective country. 

#### 2.6.5. Processing in the European Economic Area (EEA)

For Visitor and/or User with accounts located in European Data Region, all processing of Personal Data is performed in accordance with privacy rights and regulations following the EU Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 (the Directive), and the implementations of the Directive in local legislation. From May 25th, 2018, the Directive and local legislation based on the Directive will be replaced by the Regulations (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of Personal Data and on the free movement of such data, known as the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and the Company's processing will take place in accordance with the GDPR.

## 3\. _Data Security_

We take measures to protect the transmission of all sensitive end-user information. We make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems. Nevertheless, We cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party ‘hackers’ from illegally obtaining this information. We take all reasonable measures to prevent such breaches of security, but given the resourcefulness of cyber-criminals, We are unable to guarantee that our security is one hundred percent (100%) breach-proof. You assume the risk of such breaches to the extent that they occur despite our reasonable security measures.

## 4\. _Retention and deletion_

The Company will not retain data longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations. For User data, Users with an active account will therefore have the responsibility to delete data when required. When a user’s account is terminated or expired, all Personal Data collected through the platform will be deleted, as required by applicable law.

## 5\. _Acceptance of these Conditions_

We assume that all Visitors and/or Users and/or Partners have carefully read this document and agree to its contents. If someone does not agree with this Privacy Policy, it should refrain from using the Website and/or the services. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy as necessity. We encourage Visitors and/or Users to frequently check this page for any changes. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications. Continued use of the Website and/or the services after any changes to these conditions implies acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. 

## 6\. _Our Legal Obligation to Disclose Personal Data_

We will reveal a Visitor and/or User’s Personal Data without his/her prior permission only when we have reason to believe that the disclosure of this information is required to establish the identity of, to contact or to initiate legal proceedings against a person or persons who are suspected of infringing rights or property of the Company or to others who could be harmed by the user’s activities or of persons who could (deliberately or otherwise) transgress upon these rights and property. We are permitted to disclose Personal Data when we have good reason to believe that this is legally required.

## _6\. Commitment to Legal-Age Usage_

Protecting children from adult content is especially important. For that reason, We do not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the Website from persons under 18 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 18. If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use or access the Website at any time or in any manner. If We learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 18 years of age has been collected, appropriate steps will be taken to delete this information.

## _7\. Data Protection Officer_

If you have any further questions regarding the data collects, or how we use it, please contact us by email at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

We use cookies to make sure you can have the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we assume that you will be happy with it. Ok
